macissues.com 2003-06-20

# MacNut | Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  
Please read and understand the following privacy statement before using any information or services provided by MacNut Magazine. This is posted to protect both you and MacNut Magazine.

We believe your privacy on the Internet, and elsewhere, is of great importance. Because MacNut Magazine gathers some information about its users, it is important for you to fully understand the terms and conditions regarding the collection and use of that information. This privacy policy discloses what information is gathered, how it is used, and how you can correct, change, or update this information.

This privacy policy will answer the following questions:

  * What personally identifiable information does MacNut Magazine collect?
  * How does MacNut Magazine use personally identifiable information?
  * With whom, if anyone, does MacNut Magazine share this information?
  * What options are available regarding the collection, use, and distribution of this information?
  * How does MacNut Magazine allow one to correct, change, or update this information?
  * What security is in place to minimize the risk of loss, misuse, or alteration of this information?

What personally identifiable information does MacNut Magazine collect?   
When browsing the MacNut Magazine website, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer is collected and stored in a log file. The IP address is used to help analyze trends, streamline the performance of the webserver, administer the website, and to gather broad statistical information for aggregate use. However, IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information.

When you subscribe to MacNut Magazine, some personal information is collected. During the registration process, MacNut Magazine requires you to provide your name and e-mail address. At any point where MacNut Magazine collects personal information, a link will be provided to this privacy policy.

Top

How does MacNut Magazine use personally identifiable information?  
MacNut Magazine uses any information voluntarily provided by members to improve the experience of using the website and services provided by MacNut Magazine.

MacNut Magazine uses tracking information (log files) to determine which portions of the site are more popular than others, but what individual members read is not tracked. Likewise, when a search is performed with the MacNut Magazine search engine, the search terms used are recorded, but individual search terms are not connected to individual members. Both of these tracking methods are helpful to determine the relative popularity of individual pages and to improve the accuracy of the search engine.

MacNut Magazine also creates aggregate reports on member demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors, and business partners. 

This results in advertising campaigns that are more effective for advertisers. However, MacNut Magazine does not track the usage patterns of individual members, and therefore, advertisers, sponsors, and business partners will not be able to tell that a specific user clicked on a particular advertisement.

Top

With whom, if anyone, does MacNut Magazine share this information?  
MacNut Magazine and MacNut. LLC, is the sole owner of all information collected from the website and services provided by MacNut Magazine. MacNut Magazine will not sell, share, or rent any personally identifiable information to any third-parties, except under specific circumstances, as described below.

_Legal:_ In the event that you are allegedly involved in any type of criminal activity using the MacNut Magazine website or services, and MacNut Magazine is subpoenaed to release your membership information, MacNut Magazine is required by law to comply with the subpoena. MacNut Magazine also reserves the right to disclose membership information in special cases when releasing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against any individual who has blatantly or repeatedly violated the Terms of Use agreement.

_Advertising:_ MacNut Magazine does not sell or rent information about individual users to anyone for any reason. However, MacNut Magazine does share aggregate demographic information with advertisers, sponsors, and business partners, but this information is not linked to any personal information that could identify any individual person. In the unlikely event that MacNut Magazine or substantially all of its assets are acquired, subscription information will be one of the transferred assets.

MacNut Magazine does however send out monthly advertising notices to the subscription list as a whole, based on contracts with advertisers.

_Link Policy:_ MacNut Magazine allows and encourages links to any public page, as long as the linked page does not appear within a frame that prevents bookmarking it. 

Top

What options are available regarding the collection, use, and distribution of this information?  
Companies that advertise on MacNut Magazine may use cookies to make it easier to track banner performance. While MacNut Magazine uses cookies to store login information, cookies received with advertisements are collected by the advertising companies, and MacNut Magazine does not have any access to this information.

MacNut Magazine provides advertisers, sponsors, and business partners with aggregate information only, in such a manner that neither the client nor MacNut Magazine can associate any individual or their associated membership profile within the aggregate information.

Top

How does MacNut Magazine allow one to correct, change, or update this information?  
MacNut Magazine makes it simple to correct, change, or update user information via e-mail. If you need to correct, change, or update any of your subscription information, please use the following instructions.

To correct, change, or update your name or e-mail address, go to our subscription page manage your subscription.

Top

What security is in place to minimize the risk of loss, misuse, or alteration of this information?  
MacNut Magazine relies on the Service Provider to provide physical security for MacNut Magazine. Although MacNut Magazine takes every possible precaution with personal information, all visitors shall follow standard security procedures when accessing and using the MacNut Magazine website and services provided by MacNut Magazine. By using the website, you acknowledge that MacNut Magazine has neither responsibility for nor control of the communications lines used to access the website and services since such lines are provided by a third-party public utility, and that the security of transmissions to and from the website and services are not the responsibility of MacNut Magazine.

Privacy Statement Notice & Changes  
All members of MacNut Magazine should be aware that the MacNut Magazine website includes links to other sites. Please be aware that MacNut Magazine is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. It is in your own best interest to be aware when you leave the MacNut Magazine website and to read the privacy policies of each website that collects personally identifiable information from its visitors. The privacy policy posted on MacNut Magazine applies only to MacNut Magazine

MacNut Magazine reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. In the event that a decision is made to change the privacy policy, a notice regarding the change will be posted on the MacNut Magazine homepage so that you will always be aware of what information MacNut Magazine collects, how it is used, and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed. If at any point MacNut Magazine decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, you, and all other members, will be notified by email. All members will have a choice as to whether or not MacNut Magazine uses their information in this different manner. MacNut Magazine will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If you have any additional questions regarding MacNut Magazine and your privacy, simply send a message to [info@mac-nut.com](mailto:info@mac-nut.com "Email for additional information") . Thank you for supporting MacNut Magazine!

Top

ages/img_leftCol_horizDivider.gif" alt="horizDivider" width="160" height="11" /> Subscribe/Unsubscribe  
Click here to subscribe, or  
unsubscribe, to MacIssues.   

Recent MacIssues Reviews  
Software Reviews  
 Cinema 4D Version 8  
 DEVONthink  
 DVDweddings.  
 Konfabulator  
 Meteorologist  
 Power Over Ethernet 

Hardware Reviews  
ABSplus Automatic Backup System 40GB Portable  
BlueTooth

Game Reviews  
Shadowbane

Tips  
Digital Photography
